Finding Aid for the Honey Alexander Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Honey Alexander Papers
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0734.1
25.2 linear_feet
- Series I: Correspondence
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1979
    - A – Aller (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American Express – Atkinson (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Ayres – Beasley (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Beeker – Border Guild (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Boyd – Bradshaw (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Branstetter – Cabage (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Cade – Cannon (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Carter – Centennial Club (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Chandler – Crisci (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Critzer – Culbertson (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Damron – Dotson (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - DuPont – Espil (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Fain – Franklyn (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Freeman – Gotzians (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Green – Hardison (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Harlan – Hess (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Hickman – Ingram (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Innkeeper – Jones (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Karney – Koski (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Lamm – Light (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Littleton – Love (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Madden – Massa (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Massey – McMillan (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - McNabb – Monroe (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Montgomery – Moynihan (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Nail – Padgett (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Park – Prince (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1979
    - Ramsey – Roberson (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Robinson – Rose (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Rosenberg – Scoggin (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Scott – Shields (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Simmons – Smithson (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Spain – Townsen (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Train – Vann (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Vogel – Warren (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Webb – Wilson (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Wilson – Woodworth (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Wright – Zerfoss (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Invitation Regrets – Alpha Psi – Bowron (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Invitation Regrets – Buehrens – Cash (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Invitation Regrets – Centennial Club – Edmands (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Invitation Regrets – Estabrook – McNeilly (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Invitation Regrets – Memphis Country Club – Sanders (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Invitation Regrets – Sansom – Weingart (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Residence – Alexander – Wilson (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - County Judge Letters / IYC (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - International Year of the Child (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1980
    - Abdell – Allen (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - American Legion Auxiliary – St. Andrews Cathedral (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Armacher – Ayres (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Babcock – Bauman (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Beall – Bowman (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Bradley – Bryan (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Buhler – Byles (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Cage – Cambodia Crisis Center (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Canada – Carmichael (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Carpenter – Caulkins (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Chambers – Clover Bottom (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Coats – Cook (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Cooper – Cox (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Craddock – Cutman (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1980
    - Dann – Durrett (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Eakin – Embry (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Enale – Evans (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Fain – Fels (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Fewell – Flora (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Foglesong – Furrow (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Galyon – Gazebo (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Gentry – Gilmer (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Glover – Grifey (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Griffin – Gupton (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Haga – Harrison (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Hartzog – Hendrix (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Hess – Hon (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1980
    - Hood – Hutchison (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Ingram – Ishmael (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Jackson – Joy (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Kanao – Kimmel (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - King – Kramer (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Lader – Ledford (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Lee – Lis (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Littlefield – Lyle (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - McCall – McMackin (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - McNabb – McNeil (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Madden – Maryville College (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Masker – Moore (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Morris – Music (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1980
    - Neilson – Norfleet (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Northcutt – Nutrition (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Oates – Owen (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Painter – Perkins (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Person – Peterson (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Phelan – Pyron (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Quie (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Race – Reiss (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Reynolds – Robertson Academy (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Robinson – Rust (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Sachs – Scott (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Schwartz – Shafer (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Shakespeare Company – Simpson (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Sinor – Smithson (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1979
    - Southall – Spencer (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Soreen – Stevens (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Stewart – Swainey (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tanksley – University of Tennessee (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Tennessee Women’s Network – Thomson (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Thornburgh – Tyree (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - U – Underwood (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Vance – Vayda (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Waddell – Ward (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Warren – Weddle (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Weeks – Wheeler (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Wherry, Sally (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - White – Wills (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Wilson – Wisner (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Witt – Wyeth (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Young – YMCA (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Z – Zimmerman (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1981
    - Abrahams – Armistead (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Arnett – Austin (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Bailey – Behm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Belck – Boehm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Boling – Brothers (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Brown – Byrne (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Caldwell – Clay (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Clement – Cooper (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Core – Cutman (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Dann – Denny (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Dettwiller – Durham (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Eadie – Ezell (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Fain – Fewell (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Fine – Fowinkle (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Freeman – Furrow (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Gardner-Howell – Gingles (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Gittings – Green (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Greer – Guthrie (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1981
    - Hagan – Hart (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Haslam – Heard (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Hendricks – Houston (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Howard – Hyde (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - I – Ingram (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Jackson Christian School – Joyner (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Kalil – Kennedy (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Kershaw – Kocen (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Laughlin – Levine (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Liau – Lonas (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Long – Luther (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - McCall – McElrath (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - McGee – McNeilly (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - MacDonald – Maze (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Meadows – Miller (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Moore – Murray (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Nichols – Norton (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Nashville – Newton (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1981
    - O’Hare – Overton (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Paffe – Parker (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Paschall – Punch (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Ragland – Register (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Rhineheart – Rooks (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Rose – Russ (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Saks – Seiberling (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Selwyn – Shelby (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Sherman – Sively (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Skipper – Smith (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Spencer – Sweeney (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Talley – Tansey (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Tarkinaton – Tennessee Women’s Political Caucus (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Terry – Tyree (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - U – University Medical Pavilion (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Vaiden – Visa (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Walker – Welleford (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Wells – Wiggins (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Williams – Worrell (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Z – Zimmerman (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1982
    - Abbott – Amstel Hotel (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Anderson – Ashmore (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Baker – Barker (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Barnes – Biggs (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Bisson – Brandon (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Branscomb – Brownie (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Bryan – Byrd (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Caldwell – Charry (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Cheek – Clark (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Cleveland – Condra (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Conner – Crook (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Crutcher – Cunningham (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Danner – Davis (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Denton – Dupree (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Early – Edwards (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Ellingboe – Exposition (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Falls – Folio (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Ford – Francis (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Frank – Freeman (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Fricks – Fukao (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Gardner – Gibbs (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Glenn – Grooms (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Hackett – Helton (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1982
    - Hendersonville – Hooper (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Horn – Hubbard (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Hudson – Hutchins (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Ingram – Ishibashi (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Jackson – Jarrett (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Jasmin – Juhasz (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Keifer – Kenner (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Kibler – Knox (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Koch – Kretehimar (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Lainhart – LaVoi (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Lee – Linn (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Long – Lynch (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - McAdams – McNeese (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Maas – Martin (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Massey – Meggs (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Merrick – Murray (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Nappi – Norris (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Northern – Nye (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Oak Ridge Boys – Owens (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Pace – Poulton (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Powers – Pueschel (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Puett – Punch (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1982
    - Radewagen – Reed (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Reese – Rivers (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Roaden – Russellville School (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Sandlin – Seals (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Seiberling – Shoemaker (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Siegel – Sizemore (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Skinner – Souture (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Spain – Stone (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Street – Swink (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Takeshita – Taylor (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Temple – Thompson (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Thurston – Toller (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Tower – Tyree (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Vaden – Volles (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Walker – Watts (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Webb – Wilburn (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Wilds – Worrell (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Yahiro – Yukon (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Z – Zimmerman (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1983
    - Abramson – Akers (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Akers – Anderson (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Andrews – Ariyoshi (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Armstrong – Azimi (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Bailey – Baker (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Bales – Barnett (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Bateman – Bearden (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Beasley – Belck (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Bellerfant – Bible (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Bicks – Blair (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Blalock – Blue (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Blythe – Branch (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Brasfield – Brown (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Brown – Broyles (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Buchanon – Burgett (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Burns – Buxton (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Caldwell – Caney (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Cannon – Cavender (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Caylor – Chapman (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1983
    - Charpio – Clement (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Cloar – Compton (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Conley – Cooper (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Cook – Cooper (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Coppinger – Core (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Cormier – Couto (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Craft – Cravens (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Crawford – Crawson (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Cullom – Curtis (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Danhop – Davis (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Davis – Dennis (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - dePaola – DeWitt (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Dickey – Driggs (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Drill – Durrett (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Eadie – Earthman (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Eatherly – Edmonds (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Edwards – Eller (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Embroiderer’s Guild – Erickson (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Ervin – Evans (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Ewell – Exum (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1983
    - Fairweather – Fulton (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Galloway – Gleason (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Godsey – Gump (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Haas – Hedge (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Helton – Hutchinson (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Ikard – Irwin (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Jackson - Justice (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1983
    - Kalil – Keys (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Kibler – Kruse (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Lader – Lynch (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Mabley – McElrath (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - McGranaghan – Mitchell (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Molbach – Murphy (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Nakamoto – Nye (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Oates – Oser (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Pace – Quillen (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1983
    - Raby – Resman (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Richardson-Williams – Rust (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Sadler – Settles (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Shell – Slater (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Smith – Squire (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Stark – Sweaney (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Talley – Tutt (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1983
    - Vance – Vaughn (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Wade – Whitson (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Wiggs – Wyckoff (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Yamaguchi – Zagel (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Invitations and Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Invitations and Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Letters and Postcards (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Letters and Postcards (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1984
    - Acuff – Alter (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Ambiance – Avant (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Bahlman – Bass (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Beasley – Bland (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Blue – Boykin (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Brandon – Broyles (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Buck – Bundy (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Burchfield – Butler (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Cabot – Caney (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Cannon – Causey (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Celeste – Clay (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Cloud – Cozart (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Craddock – Cullom (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Culpepper – Cupp (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Darrow – Devine (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Dokecki – Durham (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1984
    - Eakin – E.A.R. Foundation (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Easter Seals – Ervin (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Fain – Folio (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Foshee – Furrow (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Gaiser – Gettys (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Glascock – Goldman (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Gooch – Gulbenk (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Hackett – Hargrove (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Harris – Haslam (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Hatch – Hindle (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Hines – Holt (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Horn – Howell (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Hudson – Hyatt (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Ingram – Ishihara (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Jackson – Jennings (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Jenson – Jones (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Kappa Alpha Theta – Kibler (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - King – Kurek (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Lader – Lavine (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Lawhead – LeBien (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1984
    - Lee – Ludlow (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - McDow – McWherter (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Madlock – Margraf (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Martin – Merritt (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Metzgar – Miller (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Mitchell – Morris (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Morton – Music City (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Nash – Norris (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - O’Brien – Overton (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Pacesetters – Parks (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Parrish – Peters (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Petty – Prinz (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Prior – Punch (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Raby – Rennicke (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Rense – Robb (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Robert – Robinson (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Rodgers – Ryan (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1984
    - Saint Peter Home for Children – Sergent (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Shahan – Sloan (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Smith – Stein (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Steorts – Swegan (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Tallent – Thompson (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Thornburgh – Verstandig (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Wadlington – Westminister Kindergarten (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - White – Wirth (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Wolfe – Wright (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1985
    - Abe – Atiyeh (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Bair – Bush (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Caldwell – Clouse (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Cogswell – Crowell (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Dancy – Durrett (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Eberling – Fuqua (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Gabel – Gulbenk (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Hagan – Hinton (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1985
    - Hollabaugh – Hurley (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Ichikawa – Junior League of Johnson City (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Kaiser – Kramer (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Lane – Lynch (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Mabley – Merritt (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Michie – Myatt (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Nappi – Oxley (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Paine – Qingcai (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Ralph – Rymer (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Sale – Sherrill (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1985
    - Simons – Sylvia (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Tallman – Verstandig (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Wallace – Wynn (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - York – Yudell (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1986
    - Adebonjo – Alexander (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Alive & Well – Ariyoshi (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Armour – Austin (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Baines – Barun (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Bass – Beard (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Beck – Bernard (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Berryhill – Boner (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Bosley – Brinkman (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Broadfoot – Bruce (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Brummette – Buckingham (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Buckley – Byrd (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Cabbage – Carson (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Carter – Churchwell (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Cigarran – Clinton (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Clodius – Coward (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Cox – Cuomo (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - D.A.R. – Davis (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Dean – DiPrete (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Dodson – Doyle (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Dresang – Dykes (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Echols – Elam (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Elliott – Evans (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Fabian – Floyd (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Foley – Fuqua (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1986
    - Adebonjo – Alexander (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Alive & Well – Ariyoshi (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Armour – Austin (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Baines – Barun (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Bass – Beard (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Beck – Bernard (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Berryhill – Boner (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Bosley – Brinkman (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Broadfoot – Bruce (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Brummette – Buckingham (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Buckley – Byrd (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Cabbage – Carson (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Carter – Churchwell (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Cigarran – Clinton (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Clodius – Coward (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Cox – Cuomo (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - D.A.R. – Davis (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Dean – DiPrete (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Dodson – Doyle (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Dresang – Dykes (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Echols – Elam (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Elliott – Evans (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Fabian – Floyd (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Foley – Fuqua (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - First Lady – Correspondence, 1986
    - Padgett – Perkinson (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Perrin – Pittard (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Plante – Punch (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Q – Quinn (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Radcliffe – Regen (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Rense – Robertson (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Robinson – Rymer (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Sallee – Savage (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Schadt – Schroeder (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Sheehan – Sisson (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Sivley – Slack (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Slaughter – Smith (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Smyre – Sperling (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Starnes – Swartzbaugh (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Tallent – Tatham (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Taylor – Turner (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - U – Usair (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Vanderbilt – Vickery (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Walker – Wampler (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Ward – Warren (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Waterman – Wells (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Werthan – Wirth (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Wood – Wyre (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Yago – YMCA (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - First Lady – Correspondence - Regrets, 1980-1986
    - Regrets (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Regrets (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Regrets (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Regrets (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Regrets (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Series II: Healthy Children Initiative
  - First Lady – Healthy Children Initiative, 1982-1987
    - General (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - General (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - General (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - General (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - General (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - General (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - General (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - First Lady – Healthy Children Initiative, 1982-1987
    - General Subcommittees (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Nonwhite Infant Mortality Subcommittee (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - School Health Subcommittee (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Evaluation Subcommittee (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Infant Follow-up Subcommittee (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Follow-up Subcommittee (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Medical Home Subcommittee (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Social Environment Subcommittee (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Involvement Subcommittee (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - First Lady – Healthy Children Initiative, 1982-1987
    - Medical Advisory Subcommittee (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Education Subcommittee (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Education Subcommittee (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Education Subcommittee (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - General – Legal Size (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - General – Legal Size (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1984 January 25 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1984 May 3 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1984 October 3 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1985 January 30 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Governor’s Task Force, 1985 May 22 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Governor’s Task Force – Final Recommendations (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - First Lady – Healthy Children Initiative, 1982-1987
    - “State Plan for Prenatal Service Tennessee Department of Public Health”, 1982-1983 (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - “State Plan for Prenatal Service Tennessee Department of Public Health”, 1982-1983 (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - “Take Care of Your Baby from the Start”, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Parents Anonymous Helpline Information, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Memos to Healthy Children Management Team from Marguerite Sallee, 1984 December (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - “Tennessee’s Most Precious Resource” – circa, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Suggestions for Community Action, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Genetics and Perinatal Fact Sheet, 1984 Spring (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Local Resources for the Pregnant Teenager, 1984 Spring (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Information Sheet, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Healthy Children Poster Contest, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)